Soft lips,
شفاه ناعمة
red ears,
آذان حمراء
and white t-shirt.
وقميص أبيض.
=Who Stole My Kiss=
= من سرق قبلتي =
=Episode 1=
= الحلقة 1 =
The first kiss is so nice of a feeling.
القبلة الأولى لطيفة للغاية من الشعور.
It was just a dream.
لقد كان مجرد حلم.
But,
لكن،
the dream was so real.
كان الحلم حقيقيًا جدًا.
The dream was worth it.
كان الحلم يستحق كل هذا العناء.
Plaster bandage?
ضمادة الجص؟
(This is not a dream.)
(هذا ليس حلم.)
Who kissed me?
من قبلني؟
(Li Xiaoxiao, Han Tingting's friend) You were kissed?
(Li Xiaoxiao ، صديق Han Tingting) هل تم تقبيلك؟
(Tarot card reading part-timer)
(قراءة بطاقة التارو بدوام جزئي)
Let me count for you.
دعني أعول لك.
Tell me who had
قل لي من كان
an intimate touch with you
لمسة حميمة معك
last night.
اخر مساء.
(Last night,)
(اخر مساء،)
(the project team was having a meal together.)
(كان فريق المشروع يتناول وجبة معًا).
(The whole team was there.)
(كان الفريق بأكمله هناك).
The project is going well
المشروع يسير على ما يرام
because of everyone's effort,
بسبب جهود الجميع ،
especially our main planner.
خاصة مخططنا الرئيسي.
My master, Lu Bai.
سيدي لو باي.
His relationship with you is different.
علاقته معك مختلفة.
My master has a nickname,
سيدي لديه لقب ،
Master Stare.
سيد ستير.
When he stares at you
عندما يحدق بك
in the office,
في المكتب،
no one would even talk.
لا أحد يتكلم حتى.
(Lu Bai, Han Tingting's superior, top game producer)
(لو باي ، أفضل منتج ألعاب هان تينجتينج)
As long as he stares at me,
ما دام يحدق بي ،
I'd be terrified.
سأكون مرعوبًا.
It can't be him.
لا يمكن أن يكون هو.
Who else then?
من بعد ذلك؟
What's going on there?
ما الذي يحصل هناك؟
Lu Yuanyu?
لو Yuanyu؟
Bottoms up.
في صحتك.
Ting.
تينغ.
It could be him.
يمكن أن يكون هو.
No.
لا.
(Lu Yuanyu, intern planner)
(لو يوانيو ، مخطط متدرب)
(Cheerful young boy) Drink slowly.
(ولد صغير مرح) اشرب ببطء.
Here's a box of plant milk.
هنا علبة حليب نبات.
I'm his superior.
أنا رئيسه.
He should show me some concerns as my staff.
يجب أن يظهر لي بعض المخاوف مثل فريق العمل الخاص بي.
Who else then?
من بعد ذلك؟
This...
هذه...
This is that guy!
هذا هو ذلك الرجل!
Qin Mochi!
تشين موتشي!
(Qin Mochi, unpopular actor, candidate for love game ambassador)
(تشين موتشي ، ممثل لا يحظى بشعبية ، مرشح لسفير لعبة الحب)
Look, it's Qin Mochi.
انظر ، إنه تشين موتشي.
He's so handsome.
انه وسيم جدا.
Congratulations.
تهانينا.
What?
لما؟
He gave you flowers?
أعطاك الزهور؟
Can you stop being
هل يمكنك التوقف عن الوجود
so surprised?
فوجئت جدا؟
Our companies are collaborating.
تتعاون شركاتنا.
He gave me flowers to celebrate
أعطاني الزهور للاحتفال
the success of the project.
نجاح المشروع.
We have three suspects now.
لدينا ثلاثة مشتبه بهم الآن.
They're not bad.
إنهم ليسوا سيئين.
Han Tingting,
هان تينجتينج ،
your happy life is about to start.
حياتك السعيدة على وشك أن تبدأ.
Let's go!
لنذهب!
(Mature master, Lu Bai, cheerful disciple, Yuanyu, idol, Mochi)
(سيد ناضج ، لو باي ، تلميذ مرح ، يوانيو ، معبود ، موتشي)
(I'm starting my journey of pursuing my love.)
(بدأت رحلتي في متابعة حبي.)
Wait!
انتظر!
What if the one who kissed you
ماذا لو من قبلك
is not among the three of them?
أليس من بين هؤلاء الثلاثة؟
(It can't be these greasy men, right?)
(لا يمكن أن يكون هؤلاء الرجال دهنيين ، أليس كذلك؟)
Come to my office.
تعال الى مكتبي.
(Could it be my master?)
(هل يمكن أن يكون سيدي؟)
Master, are you looking for me?
سيدي ، هل تبحث عني؟
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
Look.
ينظر.
(Male and female protagonists' interaction setting)
(إعداد تفاعل الشخصيات من الذكور والإناث)
The design of the swivel chair in the plot has a a problem.
تصميم الكرسي الدوار في قطعة الأرض به مشكلة.
The male protagonist's interaction doesn't make sense.
تفاعل البطل الذكر لا معنى له.
I've told you many times.
لقد أخبرتك عدة مرات.
You need to try it out
أنت بحاجة لتجربتها
to experience the action.
لتجربة العمل.
Got it, master.
فهمت يا سيدي.
Although there are a few loopholes,
على الرغم من وجود بعض الثغرات ،
it's quite new and fresh overall.
إنه جديد تمامًا وجديد بشكل عام.
It should be able to be approved.
يجب أن تكون قادرة على الموافقة.
(Did he do it on purpose?)
(هل فعل ذلك عن قصد؟)
What are you thinking about?
بم تفكر؟
No, nothing.
لا لا شيء.
Master,
يتقن،
don't you have other things
ليس لديك أشياء أخرى
to talk to me?
لتتحدث معي
Check the proposal again
تحقق من الاقتراح مرة أخرى
before the meeting.
قبل الاجتماع.
(What's going on?)
(ماذا يحدث هنا؟)
(So,)
(وبالتالي،)
(the one who kissed me is not master?)
(من قبلني ليس سيدا؟)
The highlight of the project
أهم ما يميز المشروع
is creating different feelings
يخلق مشاعر مختلفة
through each story
من خلال كل قصة
to increase user experience.
لزيادة تجربة المستخدم.
Even if we set some levels in the game
حتى لو وضعنا بعض المستويات في اللعبة
that requires credit reload,
يتطلب إعادة تحميل الرصيد ،
the users might not buy it.
قد لا يشتريه المستخدمون.
The known competitors have no successful case before.
المنافسين المعروفين ليس لديهم حالة ناجحة من قبل.
No project has any successful case to back them up
لا يوجد مشروع لديه أي حالة ناجحة لدعمها
before it goes viral.
قبل أن ينتشر الفيروس.
Han Tingting.
هان تينجتينج.
You've never dated anyone before, have you?
لم تواعد أي شخص من قبل ، أليس كذلك؟
A girl who has never dated anyone
الفتاة التي لم تواعد أحدا من قبل
is the main planner.
هو المخطط الرئيسي.
How can the users feel the love?
كيف يشعر المستخدمون بالحب؟
Are you saying that
هل انت تقول هذا
only a killer can write criminal novels
فقط قاتل يمكنه كتابة روايات إجرامية
and a deity can write about fantasy?
ويمكن للإله أن يكتب عن الخيال؟
We'll do a data research
سنقوم بإجراء بحث عن البيانات
to convince the users
لإقناع المستخدمين
with sufficient details.
بتفاصيل كافية.
(Yes!)
(نعم!)
(Master's on my side.)
(ماجستير في جانبي.)
The sales performance of the project
أداء مبيعات المشروع
will be held responsible by the team.
سيتحمل المسؤولية من قبل الفريق.
Meeting is adjourned.
تم تأجيل الاجتماع.
Why did you lose your focus?
لماذا فقدت تركيزك؟
I was...
انا كنت...
The project was set.
تم تعيين المشروع.
If there's next time,
إذا كانت هناك المرة القادمة ،
you won't be leading any project.
لن تقود أي مشروع.
Compile the amendments and do it.
اجمع التعديلات وافعلها.
Got it, master.
فهمت يا سيدي.
Master is master after all.
السيد هو سيد بعد كل شيء.
His face is like
وجهه مثل
he'd never have any feelings.
لم يكن لديه أي مشاعر.
I got it now.
حصلت عليها الان.
Let alone kissing,
ناهيك عن التقبيل ،
even when we get closer than 5 cm,
حتى عندما نقترب من 5 سم ،
I feel like I'm staining him.
أشعر وكأنني تلطخه.
It was my wrong perception.
كان تصوري الخاطئ.
It can't be him.
لا يمكن أن يكون هو.
(Look at you imagining things here.)
(انظر إلى تخيل الأشياء هنا.)
(Why not you test him out?)
(لماذا لا تختبره؟)
(I need a chance to do that.)
(أحتاج إلى فرصة للقيام بذلك).
(Here's my chance.)
(ها هي فرصتي.)
Master.
يتقن.
(He's really here.)
(إنه هنا حقًا).
(What should I do?)
(ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟)
(I can't think of any)
(لا أستطيع التفكير في أي شيء)
(tricks to seduce a man)
(حيل لإغواء الرجل)
(at this critical moment.)
(في هذه اللحظة الحرجة).
(Who cares? Let's do it.)
(من يهتم؟ دعونا نفعل ذلك.)
Master, the water is so hot.
سيدي ، الماء ساخن جدا.
Can you hold it for me?
هل يمكنك الاحتفاظ بها من أجلي؟
♪Does he like you?♪
♪ هل يحبك؟ ♪
♪Don't rush to interrupt♪
♪ لا تتسرع في المقاطعة ♪
♪You're being silent♪
♪ أنت صامت ♪
♪I lost the courage to talk♪
♪ فقدت الشجاعة للحديث ♪
♪That day was a suitable timing♪
كان ذلك اليوم هو التوقيت المناسب ♪
♪I wanted to tell you♪
♪ أردت أن أخبرك ♪
♪Because you're gentle♪
♪ لأنك لطيف ♪
♪Like printed in my heart♪
♪ مثل المطبوع في قلبي ♪
♪Wanted to♪
♪ مطلوب
♪Embrace your breath♪
♪ احتضان أنفاسك ♪
♪Only you can♪
♪ أنت فقط تستطيع ♪
♪Solve the cute riddle♪
♪ حل اللغز اللطيف ♪
♪I like your♪
♪ أنا معجب بك ♪
♪Silly face♪
♪ وجه سخيف ♪
♪So happiness is always mentioned♪
♪ فدائما ما تذكر السعادة
♪It's in the bottom of my heart♪
♪ إنها في أعماق قلبي ♪
♪There are wind, rain and you♪
هناك رياح ومطر وأنت
♪Every day♪
♪ كل يوم ♪
♪You've slowly become♪
♪ لقد أصبحت ببطء ♪
♪The best weather in my eyes♪
♪ أحلى طقس في عيني ♪
♪Holding me in your arms♪
أمسكني بين ذراعيك ♪
♪I like♪
♪ أحب ♪
♪Being with you♪
التواجد معك ♪